Hello friends, in today's video I will
tell you how to permanently close ICICI Firstag
and if there is some money
left in it then how to get the refund of that money in your bank
account.  So let's
start the video.  So for that, first of all
you have to open any browser of your mobile.
Like I
open Google browser here and here
you have to search ICICI Bank. After first
type
searching, you have to
click on the first website that is visible here.
After clicking, you
will see an interface like this here.  So look here, an
option is visible, Existing Customer.
You have to click here.  After that you have to
scroll down a little here and
here you will get two options.
You have to click on the option of Individual Login.
After that you will again get two options.  So
here you will click on the option of Login by Mobile Number.
After that you have to
scroll down a little again
and here you have to enter your registered
mobile number and here you will
enter this capture on the verification code.
After entering the captcha,
click on Request OTP here.  So
after that an OTP will be sent to you.  That
OTP has to be entered here.
After entering the OTP, tick on Remember Me
and login.  After logging in,
you will see the interface
of this portal like this.  So we will zoom in a little bit here
and make it no here.
After that a popup will appear here.  This too will be cut
and removed.  After that we will zoom this page a little.
So here you
will see an option Close Account.  You have to click here.
After clicking, we will zoom a little here.
And look here, an option is
visible, I Agree.  We will tick here
and accept here.
After accepting, you will be given a form here.
You have to fill up this form.
So look in the form, the reason is being asked here.
Why do you
want to close this first one?  So here is the reason
for closing the account.  Here you will
type a reason.  So I have
typed my reason.  Basically it is written
currently not using the first tag
regularly.  You can give anything Reese.  So we will
type a reason.  After that
see the document details here.  So you have to
fill the details of your document here.
So here in the document details, the
first option you see is
Name of the person, that is, the first person whose name is mentioned,
you will enter his name here.
After that, here type Requesting for Closer ID
Proof.  So here you will see a small
icon.  Will click on this.
So you will choose one ID proof of yours.
So here I
choose a simple Aadhar card.  After that, the
second option coming here is ID proof.
I chose Aadhar card.  So here you will have to
upload a photo of Aadhar card.
So here on this side, an
interrogative icon is visible.  If you
click on this, you will see that the
document file size exists 2 MB, which means it should be
2 MB.  The size of the
document that you are uploading should be
2 MB.  take
care of it.  Less than 2 MB will work but
not more.  So, take a 2 MB size
photo of your document and
upload it by clicking on Choose File here.  Then
here's another if any.  So
if you have something other than Aadhar card,
PAN card, Voter card, or anything else, you can
choose it here and
upload it in the same process.  After that,
passbook or cancelled cheque is shown here.  You
will take a photo of your bank account passbook or if you do not want to give the passbook, you
can also give a cancelled cheque.  So in
the same way, we will
upload a photo of its passbook or cancelled cheque of 2 MB.
After that the bank account
details are coming here.  You have to fill all the details of your bank account
here one by one.
Basically, if
some money is left in the first installment, then
you have to fill up this process to get the refund of that money.
So simply you will
fill it one by one.  You will fill in your bank
details, bank name, branch name, bank
account number, etc. one by one.
So, I have filled everything one by one.
What do you have to do after that?   If you
zoom in a little here,
whatever your first account is,
it will be shown here one by one.
So you have to tick here the account which
you want to close.  So only
one is visible here because I have only one
first account, that is why only one is visible.
So this will be empty here.  You have to
tick it like this.  After that, here below
you will get the option of close account.
Here we will click on Close Account.
After clicking, we will do OK here.
After clicking OK, we will wait a little.
This will take a little processing.
After that, look here, this right icon has come.  It is
written here that the tag account
close request has been sent for
approval.  So your closing request has been
sent.  So after that it takes a
few days.  Meaning it is
written here within 10 or 12 days.
See here, the first account will be
closed in 12 days.  It is clearly written here that the
first account will be closed
in 12 days from the date of approval of the
closure request and whatever
money you have left in it, like here I have
₹835, then this amount will be transferred
to your bank account within 12 days.
So this is how you
can close your Fast Tag.